tiptechnews.com 2014-06-18

# Privacy Policy | Tip Tech News

##  **TipTechNews respects your privacy**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of TipTechNews.

**Credit card details**  
**  
**TipTechNews will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on TipTechNews.

**External Sites.**  
**  
**TipTechNews is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are suggested to read the privacy policy of external websites before revealing any personal information.

**Cookies**  
**  
**A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows TipTechNews to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and TipTechNews does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be utilized by 3rd party content providers such as RSSfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**  
**  
**While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to TipTechNews and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through TipTechNews have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

You should make contact with those providers and others straight if you have had any inquiries relating their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:semandse@gmail.com)
